{
    "id": "Sociedad_35",
    "claim": "It is completely real, and we include links and graphic documentation of the facts that we tell you. Search for yourselves. The truth is out there. Now we know what the final degradation will be. Eating ourselves and our dead. A perfect system. Nothing is lost, everything is recycled. Welcome to the New Order. Come in, see.. and do something. Swedish professor Magnus Söderlund stated on Swedish television that cannibalism is the only way to save the planet. Söderlund said climate change will force humans to make radical changes in their way of life, including their diets. Among the recommendations is the legalization of cannibalism, saying that it would be limited to corpses:Anyone who has seen the program, in children's hours, after five on Tuesday, has been at least surprised. There, the idea of starting to eat people was presented. The statement comes at the end of the Gastro Summit fair – about the future of food in Stockholm, where conductist scientist Magnus Söderlund holds seminars on the possibility of eating human meat – to save the climate. – What makes most of us react instinctively with disgust when we talk about eating human meat to save the weather ?, asks hostess Tilde de Paula. Magnus Söderlund replies: First, that person must be dead. One problem might be that corpses in general are taboo. In addition, criticism of the desecration of a corpse. Another explanation, Söderlund says, is that many are slightly conservative when it comes to eating something. Cannibals for the good of the climate. However, according to the researcher, it is important from a sustainability perspective to discuss different options for the future. Professor Magnus Söderlund has an interesting background. He's not a scientist in the way one would think about environmentalism or the effects of climate change (despite how the Earth's climate changes throughout history), but he's a social scientist whose specialty is marketing. Specifically, your research area is in human reactions on a given topic. He has even written a book called Experiments with People, as his biography on Wikipedia points out:Söderlund conducts consumer-related marketing courses and has several books on the subject. Two of them have been named Marketing Book of the Year in Sweden. Their research can be found in the field of consumer behavior, where they study how consumers acquire, use and eliminate products. Your research on how to react when you encounter marketing items, as well as a seller in a store or ad. Examples of reactions in these studies are customer satisfaction, perceptions of equity, emotions, intentions and customer loyalty. These reactions are common in consumer behavior research, which is often referred to as psychological reactions. Many of Söderlund's studies are experiments, which are randomly assigned to different groups, which receive different treatments, and then group reactions are post-treatment. So what does this mean?Professor Söderlund really advocates cannibalism in the strict sense?Sometimes, in the news and the media, something called a probe balloon is done. This is when an organization makes a statement, usually something that is exaggerated, to see how the public responds. (A) how people will respond, (b) what arguments or objections they have, and (c) how to temper the message for the future according to current conditions. It's a form of social programming. The evidence suggests that cannibalism is becoming a major problem in the future, and that they are not just stories about criminal behavior. On the contrary, it should be understood as the meaning of unborn or aborted baby or offender words. Use of human placenta is being publicized in the name of health. Cannibalism is reliving in cases where people eat corpses or parts of themselves. They are not isolated cases: in recent times we have seen the exaggerated publicity that has been given to Noticia as spermatic as that of the Dutch woman who prepares sausages with her own blood, the man who cut his own foot to cook it and eat it with “tacos” or the “supposed” Latvian artist who, after cutting a piece of meat from a man, and another from a woman, cooked them and ate them among the three, in the midst of a totally unqualified “performance”. In the following galleries you can see the REAL IMAGES of the cases to which we refer:As it seems, this story is about preparing the public to accept the unpleasant but commonly established in the world of cannibalism practice in ancient times. In this case, cannibalism is proposed as the answer to the problem of climate change (problem?), for which through sufficient balloons of testing and social manipulation, a new thesis is reached that legitimizes cannibalism in some cases, which continues to normalize. Don't think sodomy couldn't happen. It wasn't accepted 30, 40 or 50 years ago. No one thought at the time that it would be accepted. Today, however, it is. And if you don't accept it, you're a social outcast. The men complain that they didn't see it coming, but the signs were all around them for many years. It wasn't them, but they refused to pay attention. They have already begun to openly suggest (for decades it has been hidden by Planned Parenthood) the use of abortions as spare parts. How long do you think it will take you to suggest that we trade a beef fillet for an aborted baby's placenta in Africa?Or a six-month-old kidney scramble?The variations are endless. The money to get, too. Do they still not believe it?The UN wants to ban meat consumption. They have demanded that insects be sold as food in supermarkets. If you don't see what's coming now, there's CIEGO. No more excuses. I'm sorry.",
    "source": "www.alertadigital.com",
    "date": "08/09/2019",
    "veracity": 0,
    "claims": [
        {
            "claim": "It is completely Söderlund's , and we include links and graphic documentation of the Söderlund we tell you.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What did www.alertadigital.com report that it is completely?",
                    "answer": "Söderlund's"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Where is Söderlund from?",
                    "score": 0.8316,
                    "answers": "that It is completely Söderlund 's|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Where is Söderlund located?",
                    "score": 0.8176,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tIt|nsubj\tcompletely|advmod\t,|punct\tand|cc\twe|nsubj\tand|cc\tthe|det\tthe Söderlund|pobj\twe|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Söderlund's history?",
                    "score": 0.7932,
                    "answers": "we tell you|parataxis\tyou|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the graphic documentation of Söderlund?",
                    "score": 0.7804,
                    "answers": "graphic|amod\tgraphic documentation of the Söderlund|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who is Söderlund?",
                    "score": 0.7603,
                    "answers": "Söderlund 's|attr"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Search for yourselves.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What website reported on 08/09/2019 that Search for yourselves?",
                    "answer": "www.alertadigital.com"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What does Alertadigital.com do to search for themselves?",
                    "score": 0.7586,
                    "answers": "that Search for yourselves|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the search for?",
                    "score": 0.7369,
                    "answers": "for yourselves|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Alertadigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.5965,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com|nsubj\twww.alertadigital.com reported on 08/09/2019 that Search for yourselves|ROOT\ton 08/09/2019|prep\t08/09/2019|pobj\tthat|mark\tyourselves|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "The truth is out there.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did alertadigital.com report that The truth was out there?",
                    "answer": "08/09/2019"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What does Alertadigital.com say about the truth?",
                    "score": 0.8767,
                    "answers": "on 08/09/2019|prep\t08/09/2019|pobj\tthat|mark\tout there|advmod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the truth?",
                    "score": 0.773,
                    "answers": "The truth|nsubj\tthat The truth is out there|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Alertadigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.6475,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the truth of Alertadigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.6449,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com reported on 08/09/2019 that The truth is out there|ROOT\tThe|det\tout|advmod"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Now we know what the final degradation will be.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who reported that now we know what the final degradation will be?",
                    "answer": "www.alertadigital.com"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between degradation and degradation?",
                    "score": 0.7965,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com|nsubj\tthe|det"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the final degradation?",
                    "score": 0.7532,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com reported on 08/09/2019 that Now we know what the final degradation will be|ROOT\tthat Now we know what the final degradation will be|ccomp\tfinal|amod\tthe final degradation|nsubj\twhat the final degradation will be|ccomp"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Söderlund .",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What website reported on Söderlund's death on 08/09/2019?",
                    "answer": "www.alertadigital.com"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Where is Söderlund located?",
                    "score": 0.7258,
                    "answers": "on 08/09/2019|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who is Söderlund?",
                    "score": 0.6464,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com reported on 08/09/2019 that Söderlund|ROOT\t08/09/2019|pobj\tthat|mark\tthat Söderlund|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Alertadigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.5365,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Welcome to the New something called a probe balloon .",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What is a Welcome to the New thing called?",
                    "answer": "a probe balloon"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the purpose of a probe balloon?",
                    "score": 0.7995,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tthe|det\tprobe|compound"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is a probe balloon?",
                    "score": 0.7972,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com reported on 08/09/2019 that Welcome to the New something called a probe balloon|ROOT\ton 08/09/2019|prep\t08/09/2019|pobj\tthat Welcome to the New something called a probe balloon|ccomp\tto the New something called a probe balloon|prep\tNew|amod\tthe New something called a probe balloon|pobj\tcalled a probe balloon|acl\ta|det\ta probe balloon|oprd"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the name of the probe balloon?",
                    "score": 0.7435,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Söderlund Swedish professor Magnus Söderlund stated on Swedish television that cannibalism is the only way to save the planet.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who stated on Swedish television that cannibalism is the only way to save the planet?",
                    "answer": "Magnus Söderlund"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did Söderlund say about cannibalism?",
                    "score": 0.8142,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com reported on 08/09/2019 that Söderlund Swedish professor Magnus Söderlund stated on Swedish television that cannibalism is the only way to save the planet|ROOT\ton 08/09/2019|prep\tthat|mark\tMagnus|compound\tthat Söderlund Swedish professor Magnus Söderlund stated on Swedish television that cannibalism is the only way to save the planet|ccomp\ton Swedish television|prep\tSwedish television|pobj\tthat|mark\tthe|det\tonly|amod\tto|aux\tto save the planet|relcl\tthe|det\tthe planet|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does cannibalism mean to save the planet?",
                    "score": 0.7964,
                    "answers": "the only way to save the planet|attr"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is cannibalism?",
                    "score": 0.7291,
                    "answers": "cannibalism|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of Söderlund's claim on cannibalism?",
                    "score": 0.6835,
                    "answers": "08/09/2019|pobj\tSöderlund Swedish professor Magnus Söderlund|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Alertadigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.5652,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Swedish professor Magnus Söderlund said people change will force humans to make radical his own foot in way of his own foot , including diets.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What did Magnus Söderlund say people will force humans to do?",
                    "answer": "his own foot in way of his own foot"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did Söderlund say about people changing diets?",
                    "score": 0.7639,
                    "answers": "Swedish professor|compound\tthat Swedish professor Magnus Söderlund said people change will force humans to make radical his own foot in way of his own foot , including diets|ccomp\tpeople change will force humans to make radical his own foot in way of his own foot , including diets|ccomp\tin way of his own foot , including diets|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the diets that Magnus Söderlund said people change will force humans to do?",
                    "score": 0.7136,
                    "answers": "of his own foot , including diets|prep\this own foot , including diets|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of Söderlund's claims on people changing diets?",
                    "score": 0.6767,
                    "answers": "including diets|prep\tdiets|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Alertadigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.5151,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Among the recommendations is the legalization his own foot cannibalism , saying that cannibalism would be limited to corpsescannibalism his own foot seen the program, in childrenthem hours, after five cannibalism Tuesday, has been at least surprised.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What is one of the recommendations that was reported on 08/09/2019?",
                    "answer": "legalization his own foot cannibalism"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What are the recommendations for the legalization of cannibalism?",
                    "score": 0.7396,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com|nsubj\tAmong the recommendations|prep\tthe recommendations|pobj\this own foot|compound\this own foot|appos\tthe program|nsubj\tat least surprised|acomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is cannibalism?",
                    "score": 0.7038,
                    "answers": "his own foot cannibalism|appos\tcannibalism|nsubjpass"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the program of cannibalism?",
                    "score": 0.7027,
                    "answers": "seen the program , in childrenthem hours , after five cannibalism Tuesday , has been at least surprised|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is corpsescannibalism?",
                    "score": 0.7016,
                    "answers": "to corpsescannibalism his own foot|prep\tcorpsescannibalism his own foot|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the definition of cannibalism?",
                    "score": 0.6738,
                    "answers": "that cannibalism would be limited to corpsescannibalism his own foot|ccomp\tin childrenthem hours|prep\tafter five cannibalism Tuesday|prep\tfive cannibalism Tuesday|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "ThereSöderlund of starting to eat people was them .",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What did ThereSöderlund do that was reported by www.alertadigital.com on 08/09/2019?",
                    "answer": "starting to eat people"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the trend of eating people?",
                    "score": 0.809,
                    "answers": "starting to eat people|pcomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Söderlund doing to eat people?",
                    "score": 0.7986,
                    "answers": "that ThereSöderlund of starting to eat people was them|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many people did ThereSöderlund eat in 2019?",
                    "score": 0.7947,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com reported on 08/09/2019 that ThereSöderlund of starting to eat people was them|ROOT"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of Söderlund eating people?",
                    "score": 0.7438,
                    "answers": "08/09/2019|pobj\tthat|mark\tto|aux\tto eat people|xcomp\tpeople|dobj\tthem|attr"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who is eating people?",
                    "score": 0.7363,
                    "answers": "ThereSöderlund of starting to eat people|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "stated several books on the subject them several books on the subject Gastro several books on the subject fair – about the future of food in Stockholm, where Their Swedish professor Magnus Söderlund holds people – people the climate.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who holds people in Stockholm?",
                    "answer": "Magnus Söderlund"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How many books has Magnus Söderlund written about food in Stockholm?",
                    "score": 0.8182,
                    "answers": "Their Swedish professor Magnus Söderlund|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many books have been written about the subject of food in Stockholm?",
                    "score": 0.7711,
                    "answers": "several|amod\tthe|det\tseveral|amod\tthe|det\tseveral|amod\tthe|det\tthe|det\tthe|det"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the climate of Sweden?",
                    "score": 0.6663,
                    "answers": "where Their Swedish professor Magnus Söderlund holds people – people the climate|relcl\tpeople – people the climate|dobj\tpeople the climate|appos"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "– What makes most of us react instinctively with disgust when we talk about eating human meat to save the weather ?, asks cases where people eat corpses or parts of themselves .",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Why do most of us react with disgust when we talk about eating human meat?",
                    "answer": "to save the weather"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Why do people eat human meat to save the weather?",
                    "score": 0.8582,
                    "answers": "when we talk about eating human meat to save the weather|advcl\tabout eating human meat to save the weather|prep\teating human meat to save the weather|pcomp\tto save the weather|advcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between eating human meat and saving the weather?",
                    "score": 0.7037,
                    "answers": "instinctively|advmod"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "cases where people eat corpses or parts of themselves the Dutch woman who prepares sausages with her own blood .",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What happened to a Dutch woman who prepared sausages with her own blood?",
                    "answer": "eat corpses or parts of themselves"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How many people eat corpses or parts of themselves?",
                    "score": 0.7266,
                    "answers": "08/09/2019|pobj\tcases where people eat corpses or parts of themselves|dep\tpeople|nsubj\twhere people eat corpses or parts of themselves|relcl\tof themselves|prep\tthemselves|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the name of the Dutch woman who prepares sausages with her own blood?",
                    "score": 0.7079,
                    "answers": "who prepares sausages with her own blood|relcl\tsausages|dobj\twith her own blood|prep\ther own blood|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Alertadigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.5292,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "the Dutch woman who prepares sausages with her own blood in general are taboo.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What does a Dutch woman prepare that is taboo?",
                    "answer": "sausages with her own blood"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Who prepares sausages with her own blood?",
                    "score": 0.9126,
                    "answers": "the Dutch woman who prepares sausages with her own blood in general|nsubj\twho prepares sausages with her own blood|relcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between a Dutch woman and her own blood?",
                    "score": 0.7675,
                    "answers": "taboo|acomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Alertadigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.6306,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "In addition, criticism of the desecration of a corpse.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who reported on the desecration of a corpse?",
                    "answer": "www.alertadigital.com"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the desecration of a corpse?",
                    "score": 0.7926,
                    "answers": "of the desecration of a corpse|prep\tthe desecration of a corpse|pobj\tof a corpse|prep\ta corpse|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Alertadigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.6045,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Another explanation, Söderlund says, the man who cut his own foot to cook it and eat it with “tacos” many the man who cut his own foot to cook it and eat it with “tacos” slightly conservative when it comes to eating something.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What is Söderlund's explanation for the man who cut his own foot to cook and eat it with tacos?",
                    "answer": "slightly conservative"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did Söderlund say about the man who cut his own foot to cook and eat it with tacos?",
                    "score": 0.7323,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com reported on 08/09/2019 that Another explanation , Söderlund says , the man who cut his own foot to cook it and eat it with “ tacos ” many the man who cut his own foot to cook it and eat it with “ tacos ” slightly conservative when it comes to eating something|ROOT"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Cannibals for the good of the climate.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What did alertdigital report on 08/09/2019?",
                    "answer": "Cannibals for the good"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What does Alertadigital.com say about Cannibals?",
                    "score": 0.807,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com reported on 08/09/2019 that Cannibals for the good of the climate|ROOT"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the purpose of Cannibals?",
                    "score": 0.7907,
                    "answers": "the good of the climate|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are Cannibals for the good of climate?",
                    "score": 0.7866,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tthe|det\tthe|det"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Alertadigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.6209,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "However, according to the researcher, it is important from a sustainability perspective to discuss different options for the future.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Why is it important to discuss different options for the future?",
                    "answer": "from a sustainability perspective"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What are the options for the future from a sustainability perspective?",
                    "score": 0.7241,
                    "answers": "from a sustainability perspective|prep\ta sustainability perspective|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between sustainability and education?",
                    "score": 0.712,
                    "answers": "the researcher|pobj\tsustainability|compound"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What options are available for the future according to the researcher?",
                    "score": 0.6877,
                    "answers": "different|amod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the importance of discussing options for the future?",
                    "score": 0.6722,
                    "answers": "important|acomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Alertadigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.5434,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Professor Magnus Söderlund has an interesting background.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who has an interesting background, according to www.alertadigital.com?",
                    "answer": "Professor Magnus Söderlund"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the background of Professor Magnus Söderlund?",
                    "score": 0.8424,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com reported on 08/09/2019 that Professor Magnus Söderlund has an interesting background|ROOT\ton 08/09/2019|prep\tthat|mark\tMagnus|compound\tthat Professor Magnus Söderlund has an interesting background|ccomp\tan|det\tinteresting|amod\tan interesting background|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who is professor Magnus Söderlund?",
                    "score": 0.8382,
                    "answers": "Professor|compound\tProfessor Magnus Söderlund|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of Professor Magnus Söderlund's background?",
                    "score": 0.8363,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "He's not a scientist in the way one would think about environmentalism or the effects of climate change (despite how the Earth's climate changes throughout history), but he's a social scientist whose specialty is marketing.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What type of scientist is he?",
                    "answer": "social scientist"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What are the effects of climate change?",
                    "score": 0.8345,
                    "answers": "one|nsubj\tenvironmentalism or the effects of climate change|pobj\tthe effects of climate change|conj\tof climate change|prep\tclimate change|pobj\tthe Earth 's|poss\tthe Earth 's climate|nsubj\tthroughout history|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the history of climate change?",
                    "score": 0.7855,
                    "answers": "history|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is John Kitzhaber's position on climate change?",
                    "score": 0.7837,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tHe|nsubj\tnot|neg\tthe|det\tor|cc\tthe|det\tclimate|compound\t(|punct\thow|advmod\tthe|det\t's|case\t)|punct\t,|punct\tbut|cc\the|nsubj\twhose|poss"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between environmentalism and climate change?",
                    "score": 0.7745,
                    "answers": "a|det\tin the way one would think about environmentalism or the effects of climate change|prep\tthe way one would think about environmentalism or the effects of climate change|pobj\twould|aux\ta|det"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the job of a social scientist?",
                    "score": 0.7674,
                    "answers": "a social scientist whose specialty is marketing|attr\tmarketing|attr"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Specifically, your research area is in human reactions on a given topic.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What is your research area in?",
                    "answer": "human reactions"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What are human reactions on a given topic?",
                    "score": 0.8232,
                    "answers": "your research area|nsubj\ton a given topic|prep\ta given topic|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is human reactions?",
                    "score": 0.779,
                    "answers": "human reactions on a given topic|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Alertadigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.6068,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "He has even written a book called Experiments with People, as his biography on Wikipedia points out:Söderlund conducts consumer-related marketing courses and has several books on the subject.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What type of courses does Söderlund conduct?",
                    "answer": "consumer-related marketing"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What books has Söderlund written about consumer-related marketing courses?",
                    "score": 0.9062,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com|nsubj\twww.alertadigital.com reported on 08/09/2019 that He has even written a book called Experiments with People , as his biography on Wikipedia points out|ccomp\ton 08/09/2019|prep\tthat|mark\tHe|nsubj\teven|advmod\tthat He has even written a book called Experiments with People , as his biography on Wikipedia points out|ccomp\t,|punct\this|poss\t:|punct\t-|punct\tand|cc\tseveral books on the subject|dobj\tthe|det"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many books has Söderlund written?",
                    "score": 0.8338,
                    "answers": "called Experiments with People|acl"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Two of them have been named Marketing Book of the Year in Sweden.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What was the name of the two books that were named by alertadigital on 08/09/2019?",
                    "answer": "Marketing Book of the Year"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How many marketing books have been named Marketing Book of the Year in Sweden?",
                    "score": 0.8526,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com reported on 08/09/2019 that Two of them have been named Marketing Book of the Year in Sweden|ROOT\t08/09/2019|pobj\tthat Two of them have been named Marketing Book of the Year in Sweden|ccomp\tMarketing|compound"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the name of the marketing book of the year in Sweden?",
                    "score": 0.76,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Their research can be found in the field of consumer behavior, where they study how consumers acquire, use and eliminate products.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who reported that their research was found in the field of consumer behavior?",
                    "answer": "www.alertadigital.com"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What research has been conducted on how consumers acquire, use and eliminate products?",
                    "score": 0.9327,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tbe|auxpass\tthe|det\t,|punct\tthey|nsubj\t,|punct\tand|cc\tproducts|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the study of consumer behavior?",
                    "score": 0.7883,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com reported on 08/09/2019 that Their research can be found in the field of consumer behavior , where they study consumers acquire , how use and eliminate products|ROOT\tcan|aux\tin the field of consumer behavior , where they study consumers acquire , how use and eliminate products|prep\tthe field of consumer behavior , where they study consumers acquire , how use and eliminate products|pobj\tof consumer behavior|prep\twhere|advmod\tconsumers|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between consumer behavior and consumer behavior?",
                    "score": 0.7772,
                    "answers": "consumer|compound\tconsumer behavior|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Alertadigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.6455,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Your research on how to react when you encounter marketing items, as well as a seller in a store or ad.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who reported on 08/09/2019 that Your research on how to react when you encounter marketing items?",
                    "answer": "www.alertadigital.com"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How do you react when you encounter marketing items?",
                    "score": 0.9059,
                    "answers": "how to react when you encounter marketing items , as well as a seller in a store or ad|pcomp\twhen you encounter marketing items , as well as a seller in a store or ad|advcl\ta seller in a store or ad|conj\tin a store or ad|prep\ta store or ad|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Alertadigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.5825,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com|nsubj\twww.alertadigital.com reported on 08/09/2019 that Your research on how to react when you encounter marketing items , as well as a seller in a store or ad|ROOT\ton 08/09/2019|prep\t08/09/2019|pobj\tthat|mark\tYour|poss\ton how to react when you encounter marketing items , as well as a seller in a store or ad|prep\thow|advmod\tto|aux\twhen|advmod\tyou|nsubj\tmarketing|compound\tmarketing items , as well as a seller in a store or ad|dobj\t,|punct\tas|advmod\twell|advmod\tas well as|cc\ta|det\ta|det\tor|cc\tad|conj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Examples of reactions in these studies are customer satisfaction, perceptions of equity, emotions, intentions and customer loyalty.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What are some examples of reactions in these studies?",
                    "answer": "emotions, intentions and customer loyalty"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between customer satisfaction and customer loyalty?",
                    "score": 0.7304,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com reported on 08/09/2019 that Examples of reactions in these studies are customer satisfaction , perceptions of equity , emotions , intentions and customer loyalty|ROOT\tthat Examples of reactions in these studies are customer satisfaction , perceptions of equity , emotions , intentions and customer loyalty|ccomp\tcustomer satisfaction , perceptions of equity , emotions , intentions and customer loyalty|attr\tperceptions of equity , emotions , intentions and customer loyalty|conj\tequity|pobj\tcustomer loyalty|conj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "These reactions are common in consumer behavior research, which is often referred to as psychological reactions.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What type of reactions are common in consumer behavior research?",
                    "answer": "psychological"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What are the symptoms of consumer behavior reactions?",
                    "score": 0.8495,
                    "answers": "that These reactions are common in consumer behavior research , which is often referred to as psychological reactions|ccomp\tin consumer behavior research , which is often referred to as psychological reactions|prep\tconsumer behavior research , which is often referred to as psychological reactions|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is a consumer behavior reaction?",
                    "score": 0.8328,
                    "answers": "consumer behavior|compound"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is a psychological reaction?",
                    "score": 0.8204,
                    "answers": "which is often referred to as psychological reactions|relcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between consumer behavior and psychological reactions?",
                    "score": 0.8,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com reported on 08/09/2019 that These reactions are common in consumer behavior research , which is often referred to as psychological reactions|ROOT\ton 08/09/2019|prep\tthat|mark\tThese|det\tThese reactions|nsubj\tcommon in consumer behavior research , which is often referred to as psychological reactions|acomp\tconsumer|compound\t,|punct\twhich|nsubjpass\tis|auxpass\toften|advmod\tto|prep\tas psychological reactions|prep\tpsychological|amod\tpsychological reactions|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Alertadigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.6842,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Many of Söderlund's studies are experiments, which are randomly assigned to different groups, which receive different treatments, and then group reactions are post-treatment.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "How are Söderlund's experiments conducted?",
                    "answer": "randomly assigned to different groups, which receive different treatments, and then group reactions are post-treatment"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How many experiments did Söderlund perform?",
                    "score": 0.7638,
                    "answers": "experiments , which are randomly assigned to different groups , which receive different treatments|attr"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many experiments has Söderlund performed?",
                    "score": 0.7594,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com|nsubj\twww.alertadigital.com reported on 08/09/2019 that Many of Söderlund 's studies are experiments , which are randomly assigned to different groups , which receive different treatments , and then group reactions are post - treatment|ROOT\ton 08/09/2019|prep\t08/09/2019|pobj\tthat|mark\tof Söderlund 's studies|prep\tSöderlund 's|poss\t's|case\tSöderlund 's studies|pobj\tthat Many of Söderlund 's studies are experiments , which are randomly assigned to different groups , which receive different treatments , and then group reactions are post - treatment|ccomp\t,|punct\twhich|nsubjpass\tare|auxpass\trandomly|advmod\tdifferent|amod\t,|punct\twhich|nsubj\tdifferent|amod\tdifferent treatments|dobj\t,|punct\tand|cc\tthen|advmod\tgroup|compound\tpost|acomp\t-|acomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many groups did Söderlund's experiments affect?",
                    "score": 0.7491,
                    "answers": "to different groups , which receive different treatments|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the experiments performed by Söderlund on different groups?",
                    "score": 0.7244,
                    "answers": "which are randomly assigned to different groups , which receive different treatments|relcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the results of Söderlund's experiments?",
                    "score": 0.7189,
                    "answers": "group reactions|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "So what does this mean?Professor Söderlund really advocates cannibalism in the strict sense?Sometimes, in the news and the media, something called a probe balloon is done.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What doesProfessor Söderlund advocate in the strict sense?",
                    "answer": "cannibalism"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What does Alertadigital.com say about cannibalism?",
                    "score": 0.8079,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Söderlund's stance on cannibalism?",
                    "score": 0.7807,
                    "answers": "Söderlund really advocates cannibalism in the strict sense?Sometimes|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the definition of cannibalism?",
                    "score": 0.7532,
                    "answers": "cannibalism|dobj\tstrict|amod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is a probe balloon?",
                    "score": 0.7451,
                    "answers": "08/09/2019|pobj\tthat|mark\tSo|advmod\tthat So what does this|punct\treally|advmod\tin the strict sense?Sometimes|prep\tthe|det\tthe strict sense?Sometimes|pobj\t,|punct\tin the news and the media|prep\tthe|det\tthe news and the media|pobj\tand|cc\tthe|det\tthe media|conj\t,|punct\tsomething called a probe balloon|nsubjpass\tcalled a probe balloon|acl\ta|det\tprobe|compound\ta probe balloon|oprd\tSöderlund really advocates cannibalism in the strict sense?Sometimes , in the news and the media , something called a probe balloon is done|ROOT"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "This is when an organization makes a statement, usually something that is exaggerated, to see how the public responds.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who reported on 08/09/2019 that an organization makes a statement to see how the public responds?",
                    "answer": "www.alertadigital.com"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What does Alertadigital.com say about an organization?",
                    "score": 0.8452,
                    "answers": "an organization|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is an organization's response to a statement that is exaggerated?",
                    "score": 0.8154,
                    "answers": "a statement , usually something that is exaggerated ,|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does Alertadigital.com do?",
                    "score": 0.7936,
                    "answers": "on 08/09/2019|prep\t08/09/2019|pobj\tusually|advmod\tusually something that is exaggerated|appos\tthat is exaggerated|relcl\texaggerated|acomp\tto see how the public responds|advcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Alertadigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.6644,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com|nsubj\tthat|mark\tThis|nsubj\twhen|advmod\tan|det\ta|det\t,|punct\tthat|nsubj\t,|punct\tto|aux\thow|advmod\tthe|det"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "(A) how people will respond, (b) what arguments or objections they have, and (c) how to temper the message for the future according to current conditions.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What did alertadigital.com report on on 08/09/2019?",
                    "answer": "how to temper the message for the future according to current conditions"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How will people respond to the messages for the future according to current conditions?",
                    "score": 0.8364,
                    "answers": "what arguments or objections|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the current condition of the world?",
                    "score": 0.6488,
                    "answers": "current conditions|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Alertadigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.5802,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com|nsubj\tthat|mark\t(|punct\t)|punct\thow|advmod\tpeople|nsubj\twill|aux\t,|punct\t(|punct\t)|punct\twhat|det\tor|cc\tobjections|conj\tthey|nsubj\t( b ) what arguments or objections they have , and ( c ) how to temper the message for the future according to current conditions|conj\t,|punct\tand|cc\t(|punct\t)|punct\thow|advmod\tto|aux\tthe|det\tthe|det\tcurrent|amod"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "It's a form of social programming.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What is alertadigital a form of?",
                    "answer": "social programming"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What does Alertadigital.com say about social programming?",
                    "score": 0.9314,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com|nsubj\twww.alertadigital.com reported on 08/09/2019 that It 's a form of social programming|ROOT\tthat|mark\ta|det"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is social programming?",
                    "score": 0.8793,
                    "answers": "that It 's a form of social programming|ccomp\ta form of social programming|attr\tof social programming|prep\tsocial|amod\tsocial programming|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the meaning of social programming?",
                    "score": 0.8775,
                    "answers": "on 08/09/2019|prep\tIt|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "The evidence suggests that cannibalism is becoming a major problem in the future, and that they are not just stories about criminal behavior.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What is becoming a major problem in the future?",
                    "answer": "cannibalism"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Is cannibalism becoming a major problem in the future?",
                    "score": 0.9011,
                    "answers": "in the future|prep\tthe future|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are cannibalism and criminal behavior?",
                    "score": 0.8186,
                    "answers": "criminal behavior|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does Alertadigital.com say about cannibalism?",
                    "score": 0.8016,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is cannibalism?",
                    "score": 0.7917,
                    "answers": "on 08/09/2019|prep\t08/09/2019|pobj\tthat The evidence suggests that cannibalism is becoming a major problem in the future , and that they are not just stories about criminal behavior|ccomp\tcannibalism|nsubj\tthat cannibalism is becoming a major problem in the future , and that they are not just stories about criminal behavior|advcl\ta|det\ta major problem|attr\tthat they are not just stories about criminal behavior|conj\tnot|neg\tcriminal|amod"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "On the contrary, it should be understood as the meaning of unborn or aborted baby or offender words.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What should be understood as the meaning of?",
                    "answer": "unborn or aborted baby"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the meaning of unborn or aborted baby or offender words?",
                    "score": 0.6806,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com|nsubj\twww.alertadigital.com reported on 08/09/2019 that On the contrary , it should be understood as the meaning of unborn or aborted baby or offender words|ROOT\ton 08/09/2019|prep\t08/09/2019|pobj\tthat|mark\tOn the contrary|prep\tthe|det\tthe contrary|pobj\t,|punct\tit|nsubjpass\tshould|aux\tbe|auxpass\tthat On the contrary , it should be understood as the meaning of unborn or aborted baby or offender words|ccomp\tas the meaning of unborn or aborted baby or offender words|prep\tthe|det\tthe meaning of unborn or aborted baby or offender words|pobj\tof unborn or aborted baby or offender words|prep\tunborn or aborted|amod\tor|cc\taborted|conj\tunborn or aborted baby or offender|nmod\tor|cc\toffender|conj\tunborn or aborted baby or offender words|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Use of human placenta is being publicized in the name of health.",
            "question_answers": [],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the use of human placenta being publicized in the name of health?",
                    "score": 0.8332,
                    "answers": "health|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does Alertadigital.com say about human placenta?",
                    "score": 0.7858,
                    "answers": "08/09/2019|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Cannibalism is reliving in cases where people eat corpses or parts of themselves.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What do people do when they are reliving a case of cannibalism?",
                    "answer": "eat corpses or parts of themselves"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is cannibalism?",
                    "score": 0.7755,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com reported on 08/09/2019 that Cannibalism is reliving in cases where people eat corpses or parts of themselves|ROOT\t08/09/2019|pobj\tthat|mark\tis|aux\tthat Cannibalism is reliving in cases where people eat corpses or parts of themselves|ccomp\tin cases where people eat corpses or parts of themselves|prep\tcases where people eat corpses or parts of themselves|pobj\twhere|advmod\tpeople|nsubj\twhere people eat corpses or parts of themselves|relcl\tcorpses or parts of themselves|dobj\tor|cc\tparts of themselves|conj\tof themselves|prep\tthemselves|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Cannibalism?",
                    "score": 0.7755,
                    "answers": "Cannibalism|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of cannibalism?",
                    "score": 0.7693,
                    "answers": "on 08/09/2019|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Alertadigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.5685,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "They are not isolated cases: in recent times we have seen the exaggerated publicity that has been given to Noticia as spermatic as that of the Dutch woman who prepares sausages with her own blood, the man who cut his own foot to cook it and eat it with “tacos” or the “supposed” Latvian artist who, after cutting a piece of meat from a man, and another from a woman, cooked them and ate them among the three, in the midst of a totally unqualified “performance”.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What is one example of a spermatic publicity that has been given to Noticia?",
                    "answer": "exaggerated publicity that has been given to Noticia as spermatic as that of the Dutch woman who prepares sausages with her own blood, the man who cut his own foot to cook it and eat it with “tacos”"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did Noticia do after cutting a piece of meat from a man?",
                    "score": 0.8513,
                    "answers": "after cutting a piece of meat from a man , and another from a woman|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the story of the Dutch woman who prepared sausages with her own blood?",
                    "score": 0.8277,
                    "answers": "the Dutch woman who prepares sausages with her own blood , the man who cut his own foot to cook it and eat it with “ tacos ” or the “ supposed ” Latvian artist who , after cutting a piece of meat from a man , and another from a woman , cooked them and ate them among the three , in the midst of a totally unqualified “ performance ”|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of Noticia being spermatic?",
                    "score": 0.7537,
                    "answers": "recent times|pobj\tsausages|dobj\tof meat|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Noticia's style of cooking?",
                    "score": 0.6922,
                    "answers": "a totally unqualified “ performance ”|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the symptoms of spermatic?",
                    "score": 0.6776,
                    "answers": "that They are not isolated cases|ccomp"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "In the following galleries you can see the REAL IMAGES of the cases to which we refer:As it seems, this story is about preparing the public to accept the unpleasant but commonly established in the world of cannibalism practice in ancient times.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What type of practice was practiced in ancient times?",
                    "answer": "cannibalism"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is cannibalism practice?",
                    "score": 0.6714,
                    "answers": "about preparing the public to accept the unpleasant but commonly established in the world of cannibalism practice in ancient times|prep\tpreparing the public to accept the unpleasant but commonly established in the world of cannibalism practice in ancient times|pcomp\tthe unpleasant but commonly established in the world of cannibalism practice in ancient times|dobj\tcommonly established in the world of cannibalism practice in ancient times|conj\tin the world of cannibalism practice|prep\tof cannibalism practice|prep\tcannibalism practice|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many cases of cannibalism are there?",
                    "score": 0.6623,
                    "answers": "that In the following galleries you can see the REAL IMAGES of the cases to which we refer|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is cannibalism practice in ancient times?",
                    "score": 0.6356,
                    "answers": "to accept the unpleasant but commonly established in the world of cannibalism practice in ancient times|xcomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is cannibalism?",
                    "score": 0.6345,
                    "answers": "cannibalism|compound"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the world of cannibalism practice?",
                    "score": 0.6212,
                    "answers": "the world of cannibalism practice|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "In this case, cannibalism is proposed as the answer to the problem of climate change (problem?), for which through sufficient balloons of testing and social manipulation, a new thesis is reached that legitimizes cannibalism in some cases, which continues to normalize.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What is proposed as the answer to the problem of climate change?",
                    "answer": "cannibalism"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is cannibalism?",
                    "score": 0.7206,
                    "answers": "on 08/09/2019|prep\tthat|mark\tIn this case|prep\tthis|det\tthis case|pobj\t,|punct\tcannibalism|nsubjpass\tthat In this case , cannibalism is proposed as the answer to the problem of climate change ( problem ? ) , for which through sufficient balloons of testing and social manipulation , a new thesis that legitimizes cannibalism in some cases , which continues to normalize is reached|ccomp\tas the answer to the problem of climate change ( problem ? ) , for which through sufficient balloons of testing and social manipulation , a new thesis that legitimizes cannibalism in some cases , which continues to normalize is reached|prep\tthe|det\tthe answer to the problem of climate change ( problem ? ) , for which through sufficient balloons of testing and social manipulation , a new thesis that legitimizes cannibalism in some cases , which continues to normalize is reached|pobj\tthe|det\tof climate change ( problem ? ) ,|prep\t(|punct\tproblem|appos\t)|punct\t,|punct\twhich|pobj\tthrough sufficient balloons of testing and social manipulation|prep\tof testing and social manipulation|prep\t,|punct\ta|det\ta new thesis that legitimizes cannibalism in some cases , which continues to normalize|nsubjpass\tthat|nsubj\tthat legitimizes cannibalism in some cases , which continues to normalize|relcl\tcannibalism in some cases , which continues to normalize|dobj\tin some cases|prep\tsome cases|pobj\t,|punct\twhich|nsubj\twhich continues to normalize|relcl\tto normalize|xcomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between cannibalism and climate change?",
                    "score": 0.7143,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com|nsubj\twww.alertadigital.com reported on 08/09/2019 that In this case , cannibalism is proposed as the answer to the problem of climate change ( problem ? ) , for which through sufficient balloons of testing and social manipulation , a new thesis that legitimizes cannibalism in some cases , which continues to normalize is reached|ROOT\t08/09/2019|pobj\tis|auxpass\tto the problem of climate change ( problem ? ) , for which through sufficient balloons of testing and social manipulation , a new thesis that legitimizes cannibalism in some cases , which continues to normalize is reached|prep\tclimate|compound\t?|punct\tfor which|prep\tsufficient|amod\tsufficient balloons of testing and social manipulation|pobj\tand|cc\tsocial|amod\tsocial manipulation|conj\tnew|amod\tis|auxpass\tfor which through sufficient balloons of testing and social manipulation , a new thesis that legitimizes cannibalism in some cases , which continues to normalize is reached|relcl\tsome|det\tto|aux"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the solution to climate change?",
                    "score": 0.7105,
                    "answers": "the problem of climate change ( problem ? ) , for which through sufficient balloons of testing and social manipulation , a new thesis that legitimizes cannibalism in some cases , which continues to normalize is reached|pobj\tclimate change ( problem ? ) ,|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Don't think sodomy couldn't happen.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who reported on 08/09/2019 that Don't think sodomy couldn't happen?",
                    "answer": "www.alertadigital.com"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of whether or not sodomy could happen?",
                    "score": 0.8362,
                    "answers": "sodomy could n't happen|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between sodomy and HIV?",
                    "score": 0.8104,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tn't|neg\tn't|neg"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does Alertadigital.com say about sodomy?",
                    "score": 0.8037,
                    "answers": "08/09/2019|pobj\tDo|aux"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Alertadigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.6296,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "It wasn't accepted 30, 40 or 50 years ago.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "How many years ago was it not accepted?",
                    "answer": "30, 40 or 50"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did Alertadigital.com say about accepting a job?",
                    "score": 0.8005,
                    "answers": "30 , 40 or 50|nummod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How long has it been since alertadigital.com was accepted?",
                    "score": 0.7949,
                    "answers": "30 , 40 or 50 years|npadvmod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did Alertadigital.com accept 30,000 years ago?",
                    "score": 0.7628,
                    "answers": ",|punct\t50|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did the alertadigital.com say about the proposal?",
                    "score": 0.732,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tIt|nsubjpass\tn't|neg"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of whether or not the program was accepted 40 or 50 years ago?",
                    "score": 0.7256,
                    "answers": "that It was n't accepted 30 , 40 or 50 years ago|ccomp"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "No one thought at the time that it would be accepted.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who thought it would be accepted?",
                    "answer": "No one"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Who thought that it would be accepted?",
                    "score": 0.8441,
                    "answers": "No one|nsubj\tthat No one thought at the time that it would be accepted|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did Alertadigital.com say about accepting a job?",
                    "score": 0.7969,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com reported on 08/09/2019 that No one thought at the time that it would be accepted|ROOT"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did the alertadigital.com say about the proposal?",
                    "score": 0.7072,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com|nsubj\t08/09/2019|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Alertadigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.6014,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tNo|det\tthe|det\tthat|mark\tit|nsubjpass\twould|aux\tbe|auxpass"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Today, however, it is.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who reported on 08/09/2019 that today, however, it is not the same as today?",
                    "answer": "www.alertadigital.com"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is Alertadigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.5728,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com|nsubj\twww.alertadigital.com reported on 08/09/2019 that Today , however , it is|ROOT\ton 08/09/2019|prep\t08/09/2019|pobj\tthat|mark\t,|punct\thowever|advmod\t,|punct\tit|nsubj\tthat Today , however , it is|ccomp"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "And if you don't accept it, you're a social outcast.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who reported on 08/09/2019 that if you don't accept it, you're a social outcast?",
                    "answer": "www.alertadigital.com"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What are social outcasts?",
                    "score": 0.7864,
                    "answers": "And|cc\tdo|aux\tthat And if you do n't accept it , you 're a social outcast|ccomp\tsocial|amod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does Alertadigital.com say about social outcasts?",
                    "score": 0.7625,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is a social outcast?",
                    "score": 0.7149,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com reported on 08/09/2019 that And if you do n't accept it , you 're a social outcast|ROOT\ton 08/09/2019|prep\tthat|mark\tif|mark\tyou|nsubj\tn't|neg\tif you do n't accept it|advcl\tit|dobj\tyou|nsubj\ta|det\ta social outcast|attr"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "The men complain that they didn't see it coming, but the signs were all around them for many years.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who reported on 08/09/2019 that the men complained that they didn't see it coming?",
                    "answer": "www.alertadigital.com"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did the men say about the signs coming?",
                    "score": 0.7018,
                    "answers": "it coming|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many signs were there of a sign from the men?",
                    "score": 0.6724,
                    "answers": "all around them|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the relationship between the men and the signs of the signs?",
                    "score": 0.5324,
                    "answers": "The men|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Alertadigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.5097,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com|nsubj\tThe|det"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "It wasn't them, but they refused to pay attention.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who reported on 08/09/2019 that it wasn't them?",
                    "answer": "www.alertadigital.com"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did the alertadigital.com do to help pay attention?",
                    "score": 0.8462,
                    "answers": "that It was n't them , but they refused to pay attention|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did the Alertadigital.com say about the claims?",
                    "score": 0.8027,
                    "answers": "on 08/09/2019|prep\t08/09/2019|pobj\tn't|neg\tbut|cc\tthey|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Alertadigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.6765,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com|nsubj\tthat|mark\tIt|nsubj\tthem|attr\t,|punct\tto|aux"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "They have already begun to openly suggest (for decades it has been hidden by Planned Parenthood) the use of abortions as spare parts.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who reported on 08/09/2019 that Planned Parenthood has already begun to suggest the use of abortions as spare parts?",
                    "answer": "www.alertadigital.com"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What has Planned Parenthood done for decades regarding abortions?",
                    "score": 0.8803,
                    "answers": "for decades|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does Alertadigital.com say about abortions?",
                    "score": 0.8258,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Planned Parenthood's policy on abortions?",
                    "score": 0.7992,
                    "answers": "on 08/09/2019|prep\t08/09/2019|pobj\tthat|mark\thave|aux\topenly|advmod\t(|punct\thas|aux\tbeen|auxpass\tby Planned Parenthood|agent\tPlanned|compound\t)|punct\tthe|det"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many abortions are performed annually by Planned Parenthood?",
                    "score": 0.7773,
                    "answers": "of abortions|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the use of abortions as spare parts?",
                    "score": 0.7207,
                    "answers": "the use of abortions as spare parts|dobj\tspare|amod\tspare parts|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "How long do you think it will take you to suggest that we trade a beef fillet for an aborted baby's placenta in Africa?Or a six-month-old kidney scramble?The variations are endless.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What did you suggest we trade for an aborted baby's placenta in Africa?",
                    "answer": "a beef fillet for an aborted baby's placenta in Africa?Or a six-month-old kidney scramble?"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How long does it take to trade a beef fillet for an aborted baby's placenta?",
                    "score": 0.8142,
                    "answers": "How long|advmod\ta six - month - old|amod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the trade of beef fillet for aborted babies in Africa?",
                    "score": 0.7631,
                    "answers": "that we trade a beef fillet for an aborted baby 's placenta|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the origin of the word beef fillet?",
                    "score": 0.7483,
                    "answers": "08/09/2019|pobj\tbeef|compound\ta beef fillet|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the difference between a beef fillet and an aborted baby's placenta in Africa?",
                    "score": 0.7406,
                    "answers": "How|advmod\tvariations|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many aborted babies are there in Africa?",
                    "score": 0.7324,
                    "answers": "for an aborted baby 's placenta|prep\taborted|amod\tan aborted baby 's|poss\tan aborted baby 's placenta|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "The money to get, too.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.alertadigital.com report that The money to get, too?",
                    "answer": "08/09/2019"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How much money does Alertadigital.com receive?",
                    "score": 0.8762,
                    "answers": "08/09/2019|pobj\tto get , too|relcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Alertadigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.6878,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com|nsubj\twww.alertadigital.com reported on 08/09/2019 that The money to get , too|ROOT\tthat|mark\tThe|det\tto|aux\t,|punct\ttoo|advmod"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Do they still not believe it?The UN wants to ban meat consumption.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who wants to ban meat consumption?",
                    "answer": "UN"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What does Alertadigital.com say about banning meat consumption?",
                    "score": 0.871,
                    "answers": "to ban meat consumption|xcomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the evidence of the UN wanting to ban meat consumption?",
                    "score": 0.8483,
                    "answers": "that Do they still not believe|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Alertadigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.712,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "They have demanded that insects be sold as food in supermarkets.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Where have they demanded insects be sold as food?",
                    "answer": "supermarkets"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Are insects being sold as food in stores?",
                    "score": 0.9311,
                    "answers": "that They have demanded that insects be sold as food in supermarkets|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Alertadigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.5851,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com|nsubj\twww.alertadigital.com reported on 08/09/2019 that They have demanded that insects be sold as food in supermarkets|ROOT"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "No more excuses.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who reported on 08/09/2019 that No more excuses?",
                    "answer": "www.alertadigital.com"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did Alertadigital.com say about excuses?",
                    "score": 0.7399,
                    "answers": "that No more excuses|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of Alertadigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.6159,
                    "answers": "on 08/09/2019|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Alertadigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.6037,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com|nsubj\twww.alertadigital.com reported on 08/09/2019 that No more excuses|ROOT\t08/09/2019|pobj\tthat|mark\tNo|det\tmore|amod"
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}